miaplaza.com 2016-03-14

# Always Icecream - Privacy Policy

Effective Date: This policy was last updated on July 7, 2014. 

Always Icecream is a Member of the PRIVO’s PRIVO-Cert™ Safe Harbor Certification Program (“the Program”). As a participating member in the Program, Always Icecream adheres to the strict information collection, use and disclosure requirements set forth by the Program. PRIVO is an independent, third-party organization committed to safeguarding children's personal information collected online. PRIVO aims to help parents and their children exercise control over personal information while exploring the Internet. The PRIVO certification seal posted on this page indicates that Always Icecream has established COPPA compliant privacy practices and has agreed to submit to PRIVO’s oversight and consumer dispute resolution process. If you have questions or concerns about our privacy practices, please contact us at +1 (650) 644-7753 or privacy@always-icecream.com. If you have further concerns after you have contacted us, you can contact PRIVO directly at privacy@privo.com. 

We will use reasonable efforts to comply with the stated privacy principles and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with them. We sometimes release alpha and beta versions of our products, which are further refined before the release of the final version. Because these products are still in a test phase, we may not always catch an unintended privacy issue, despite our efforts to do so. As such, we welcome user feedback on any privacy concerns you may have. In light of the above and because of the complex and constantly changing nature of our technology and business, Always Icecream does not guarantee error-free performance under this privacy policy. Always Icecream or Miaplaza, Inc., shall not be liable for any incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to this privacy policy. 

Please read this privacy policy to learn more about:   
1\. What personally identifiable information of yours is collected by Always Icecream.   
2\. The use of cookies and log files.   
3\. Children’s use of the site or app.   
4\. How the information is used.   
5\. With whom the information may be shared.   
6\. How you can access and change your account information.   
7\. What security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information collected by Always Icecream.   
8\. How to contact us. 

Always Icecream offers for its members a community designed for young girls, where they can interact with friends, practice school material, engage in learning activities, play games and view videos. The Service is provided through Always Icecream’s web site currently located at www.always-icecream.com ("Site"). Always Icecream is a service provided by miaplaza, Inc. (“Miaplaza”, also referred to in this Privacy Policy as “Miaplaza" or "Always Icecream”) of PO Box 183, Menlo Park, CA 94026 USA. 

Please note that this privacy policy is provided under, and subject to, the Always Icecream User Agreement. 

**Information Collection**   
Trial Registration:   
In order to become an Always Icecream trial user, one must first create a girl’s account on this web site. To create an account, a girl is required to provide the following information: her first name and last name initial, plus a password for her account. She also is asked to provide an email account for the parent. The parent is then sent an email and is asked to click on a link to verify the email account; however this verification is not required for the girl to start her trial membership. A parent that clicks on the verification link will be offered to register for a fully verified parental account, as discussed below in the Full Registration section. 

All girls with trial registration status only see messages that have been pre-monitored by Always Icecream. See the discussion of monitoring in the section “Communication between Users” below. Trial registration members cannot become “Real World Friends” as described below in the section “Always Icecream Friends.” 

If a parent email is verified, when the associated girl later logs on to the site, she is offered to provide her own email address. This email address may be used to notify her of pending, pre-monitored messages or of new offerings on the site. She is also offered to share her birth date, which allows customization of her experience on Always Icecream. 

Full Registration:   
In order to become an Always Icecream Fully Registered, paying user, one must create a parent account on this web site. To create a parent account, a parent is required to provide the following information about the parent or guardian of the girl user: parent/guardian first name and last name, email address and an account password. Further the parent is required to make at least a symbolic payment through a third-party payment service; however, Always Icecream never receives this credit card information. The payment is required to verify adult status and establish the parent’s identity. 

The girl is asked for the same sets of information with Full Registration as with Trial Registration, as discussed above. In addition, the girl user is provided a code that can be exchanged with friends to form Always Icecream Real World Friends relationships, as described in the “Always Icecream Friends” section below. 

For either registration type, Trial or Full, the girl may also provide information about herself in the child’s Profile section, such as her favorite color and what she’s doing now. Parts of this Profile are viewable by all users, while certain sections can only be seen by the girl’s friends or her own Real World Friends. As noted below, apart from communication between mutual Real World Friends, these information postings are pre-moderated for appropriateness. See below on interactions between users that are allowed for Real World Friends and Regular Friends. 

Always Icecream does not condition a child’s participation in an activity on the disclosure of more information than is reasonably necessary to participate. 

Always Icecream Friends:   
Girls want to connect with friends and it's important for building social skills; thus, we want to encourage social interaction, but we want it to be in a safer setting than is typical for the Internet. There are two types of friends on Always Icecream. 

1\. Friends/Regular Friends - Girls can become friends on Always Icecream by inviting each other to start a friendship. All communication between friends is reviewed by a site moderator (i.e., pre-moderated) before it can be read by the intended recipients to prevent inappropriate commentary and divulging of personal information. 

2\. Real World Friends - Real World Friends are friends that girls already have outside of Always Icecream. On Always Icecream Real World Friends can chat with each other and engage in other person-to-person communication that is not necessarily monitored by a site moderator. To become linked as Real World Friends on Always Icecream, both girls have to exchange their individual personal friendship codes. We currently take measures to get this to happen outside of Always Icecream. In the future we may alter this procedure, as we may come up with new, good ways of protecting the girls while encouraging social interaction. If we do, we’ll notify you first. 

A user can see, without pre-moderation, only postings made by a given user’s own Real World Friends. Moderator approval is required before Regular Friends see all other postings, such as those posted by a Regular Friend who happens also to be the Real World Friend of the user’s Real World Friend. 

A girl can end an Always Icecream friend or Real World Friend connection at any time using the friends management features of the site. 

**Cookies & Log Files**

Like most web sites, Always Icecream uses cookies and web log files to track site usage. A cookie is a tiny data file that resides on your computer that allows Always Icecream to recognize you as a user when you return to our site using the same computer and web browser. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies, you will not be able to use our website. Like the information you enter at registration or in your Profile settings, cookie and log file data is used to customize your experience on the web site. 

Always Icecream uses what is called a "session" cookie, which identifies a particular visit to the Always Icecream site. Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser. 

In addition, if you enable the automatic login feature, a "persistent" cookie stays on your computer between sessions to allow Always Icecream to recognize your user account the next time you visit. This cookie is removed if you turn off this automatic login or if you switch users. At this time Always Icecream does not use other "persistent" cookies. 

Due to the communication standards on the Internet, when you visit the Always Icecream web site we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave Always Icecream. We also receive the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system and type of web browser you are using, as well as the name of your ISP. This information is used to analyze overall trends to help us improve the Always Icecream service, but is not linked to personally identifiable information in any way. 

**Information Use**   
The information you choose to provide on this site is used to help you describe yourself to other users. In addition, Always Icecream collects certain types of information in order to operate and improve our service to you and other users. For example, we use third party Google Analytics to gather aggregate data on how many visit what Always Icecream pages, what paths are taken by members to get to Always Icecream, which browsers are used most, and other statistics. Miaplaza, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site and this third party is prohibited from sharing data. For more information on Google Analytics, click [here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). 

We transfer Information and Personally Identifiable Information between Europe (Germany) and the United States. By visiting our Web site and providing us with data, you acknowledge and agree that your personal information may be processed for the purposes identified in this policy. In addition, such data may be stored on servers located outside your resident jurisdiction, which may have less stringent privacy practices than your own jurisdiction. Please note that Always Icecream’s own policies adhere to all requirements of the United States for its users from the USA. By providing us with your data, you consent to the transfer of such data. 

**Always Icecream Communications**   
Always Icecream will communicate with you through email and notices posted on this website. These include occasional emails to inform you about various features of the service. 

**Customized Content**   
Information you provide at registration or in your Account Management section is also used to customize your experience on the web site. For example, the language used for many menu items is changed according to the setting on your Account Management page. 

**Information Sharing**   
Sharing Information with Third Parties:   
Always Icecream takes the privacy of our users very seriously. We will never sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to any third parties for marketing purposes. We will only share your personally identifiable information with third parties to carry out your instructions, to provide specific services. For instance, we use a payment and credit card processing company to bill users for subscription fees. We also use third party software development firms and server hosting services. None of these third parties retain, share, or store any personally identifiable information except to provide these services and are bound by strict confidentiality agreements which limit their use of such information. 

For more information on the third parties we work with, please email us at privacy@always-icecream.com. 

Communication between Users:   
Certain parts of the site allow for text communication between any Always Icecream user, including a member’s:   
• Profile   
• Comments to games and videos   
• Submissions to “team” chats 

Only a member’s friends see what is written in:   
• Emails   
• Certain elements of the member's Profile   
• Guestbook comments 

Only a member's Real World Friends see:   
• A chat between herself and the Real World Friend member   
• The birthday (without year) of the friend 

With the exception of communication between Real World Friends, all communication on Always Icecream is reviewed by site moderators before it is published (pre-moderation). This is to prevent inappropriate commentary and divulging of personal information to others. While our site monitors are diligent, some questionable comments may slip through; thus, please let us know if you register communication between girls that is not appropriate. 

If the member uses any of the communication function within this website and discloses personally identifiable information, you should be aware that such information could be read, collected or used by other users. While we have moderation functions, some filters and other measures in place to hinder it, we and our systems are not perfect. By verifying your account, you agree to work with us to address problems with personally identifiable information slipping through and entering the site, and you agree that Always Icecream cannot be held liable for inadvertent errors. 

Emails initiated by a girl, such as invitation emails to join her on Always Icecream, will never list her personal information apart from what is written by her for that email specifically, nor will it specify the people to whom she is directly connected unless she has added this information. Note that the sender’s first name will be added to the email so that the recipient can understand who it is from. Email text added by the girl will be pre-moderated before being included in an email. 

We will not knowingly release personal information or unmoderated user submissions to those who are not Always Icecream members. 

Legal Disclaimer:   
It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on our company or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 

**Information Safeguards**   
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, please contact us at mp-feedback@miaplaza.com 

**Accessing and Changing Your Account Information**   
You can review the personal information you provided us and make any desired changes to the information, or to the settings for your Always Icecream account, at any time by logging in to your account on the Always Icecream website and editing the account and profile information. To request that we close your account and remove your information, please send us your request and we will take care of it. Please send your request using an email account that you have registered with Always Icecream under your name. You will receive a response to requests sent to us within five business days of our receiving it. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**   
Always Icecream may update this privacy policy. In the event there are significant changes in the way we treat your personal information, we will send a notice to the primary email address specified in your Always Icecream account or by displaying a prominent notice on this site. However, it is your responsibility to review the privacy policy from time to time so you will be aware of changes. 

**Questions or Comments**   
If you have questions or comments about this privacy policy, please contact us at (650) 644-7753 or via email to johannes.ziegler@miaplaza.com, or by mail at PO Box 183, Menlo Park, CA 94026 USA.
